Finding aid for the John Fahey papers LSC.1862
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 7. Correspondence, 1968-2009
  - Miscellaneous, N, 1993-2006 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Ortiz de Landazuri, Manuel, 1978-1984 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Ortho Diagnostic Systems, 1995-1996 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Office of Federal Relations (UCLA), Washington office, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Ovary, Zoltan, 2002-2005 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Ovcak-Derzic, Stanislava, 1992-1995 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Ojo-Amaize, Emmanuel, 1985-1991 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, O, 1984-1998 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Popow, Joanna, 1989-1990 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Project Inform, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - UCLA School of Public Health, 2002-2003 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Plaegar-Marshall, Susan, 1995-2000 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Plaegar-Marshall, Susan, 1983-1995 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Prince, Harry, 1983-2006 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Panosian, Claire, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Pacific Rim Research, 1988-1989 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Pan-American Health Organization, 1996-1997 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Penny, Ronald, 1985-1997 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Peter, James, 1991-1993 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Petrov, Rem, 1984-1995 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Pharmacia, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Phanuphak, Nittaya, 1995-1998 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Passman, Leigh, 1991-1995 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Paul, William, 1995-1997 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, P, 1991-2000 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Rotheram-Borus, Mary Jane, 1997-2001 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Rowe, David, 1990-1997 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Rosenblatt, Joseph, 1976-1987 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Rosenberg, Steven, 1984-1985 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Rokos, Hartmut, 1986-1993 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Rodriguez, Christian, Fogarty, 1990-1994 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Rodriguez, Christian, 1993-2002 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Reed, Geoffrey, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Rich, Robert, 1990-2000 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Rao, V. Srinivasa, 1975-1983 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Rachelefsky, Gary, 1981-1991 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - General D. Raghunath, 1996-1997 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Rose, Noel, 1984-1999 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, R, 1993-2000 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Martinez-Maza, Otoniel, 1990-2003 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Martinez-Maza, Otoniel, 1988-1996 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Salazar, Jesus, 1983-2004 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Schroff, Robert, 1982-2004 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Seeger, Robert, 1984-2001 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Segerstrom, Suzanne, 1995-1998 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Seligmann Maxime, 1986-1996 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Shacks, Samuel, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Sadeghi, Hoss, 1995-2006 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Sercarz, Eli, 1980-2004 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Seth, Pradeep, 1999-2002 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Seth, Pradeep, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Schilling, Robert, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Schmid, Ingrid, 2000-2002 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Saxon Immunology Training, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Saxon, Andrew, 1977-2008 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Specialty Laboratories, 1986-1990 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Smith, Diane, 1987-1990 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Spondylitis Association, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Spina, Celsa, 1981-2007 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Solomon, George, 1983-2001 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Somer, Timo, 1983-1993 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Solomon, Suniti, 1994-2000 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Seth, Pradeep and Alka Arora, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Shoptaw, Steve, 2000-2001 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Solomon, Alan, 1988-2000 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Shau, Hungyi, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Stevens, Ron, 1975-1981 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Steihm, Richard, 1979-2000 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Steihm, Richard, 2004-2009 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Sternberg, Esther, 1998-2000 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Stehn, Susan, 1992-1993 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Stevens, Jack, 1977-1995 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Steckel, Richard, 1980-2007 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Thieme, Thomas, 1974-1982 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Terpinning, Marilou, 1980-1982 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Tamaroff, Marc, 1979-1983 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Targan, Stephan, 1984-1989 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Terasaki, Paul, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Taylor, Jeremy, 1985-1998 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Taylor, Shelley, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Tada, Tomio, 1991-1997 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Tourtellotte, Wallace, 1981-1990 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Traditional Chinese Medicine, 1995-1997 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Thailand, Princess Chulabhorn visit, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous, T, 1990-1998 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Ueno, Yoshiki, 1984-1994 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Uittenbogaart, Christel, 1984-2008 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Uittenbogaart, Christel, 1980-1996 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - UCLA School of Medicine, 1988-1999 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - UCLA Medical Laboratory Immunology, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - UNAIDS, 1995-1998 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, U, 1993-1996 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Venezuela, Centro Nacional de Inmunologia Clinica, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Vredevoe, Donna, 2001 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, V, 1989-2000 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Waldemann, Thomas, 1989-2009 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Wang, Hong, 1991-1999 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Weaver, Michael, 1981-1995 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Weiner, Herbert, 1990-2000 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - World Bank, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - World Health Organization, 1988-2000 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Wiley, Dorothy, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - World Health Organization, Immunology, 1988-1994 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - World Health Organization, Vaccine program, 1989-1992 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - World AIDS Foundation, 1991-1993 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Wyatt, Gail, 1999-2001 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Walden, Keri, 2001-2002 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Wall, Randy, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, W, 1996-2006 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, X, 1989-1996 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Yang, Otto, 1999-2003 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Yamamura, Yuichi, 1983-1984 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Yamashita, Naomi, 1986-2008 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Youdim, Said, 1976-1987 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous, Y, 1987-1999 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Zighelboim, Jacob, 1974-2007 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Z, 1984-2001 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Organizations -- Association of Medical Laboratory Immunologists, 1987-1994 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Organizations -- American Board of Medical Laboratory Immunology, 1981-2001 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Organizations -- California Licensing, 1977-1982 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Seth, Pradeep, 1994-1997 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Seth, Pradeep, 1997-2001 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Objects -- paperweight, plaque and "Aakhri Dastak" film, undated, 2004, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    1 DVD.
    Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. To access digital materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.